{
    "subject": "resource/Fifth_Avenue",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Upper_East_Side",
    "human_readable": "Fifth Avenue is about Upper East Side.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872484803199768,
            "question": "Is Fifth Avenue in the Upper East Side?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.97967529296875,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Fifth Avenue and the Upper East Side?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417120218276978,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Fifth Avenue and the Upper East Side?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7258766293525696,
            "question": "Where is Fifth Avenue located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7124423384666443,
            "question": "Which neighborhood is Fifth Avenue about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6790533661842346,
            "question": "What area is associated with Fifth Avenue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6493653059005737,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the location of Fifth Avenue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6165719628334045,
            "question": "Where would you find Fifth Avenue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4660497307777405,
            "question": "If you were to visit the Upper East Side, what famous street could you expect to see?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3450891077518463,
            "question": "What part of New York City is known for Fifth Avenue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fifth Avenue is about Upper East Side.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2772_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to visit the Upper East Side, what famous street could you expect to see?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2772_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you find Fifth Avenue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2772_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the location of Fifth Avenue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2772_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2772_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided includes details about the Upper East Side, including that it extends along Fifth Avenue. Therefore, the statement \"Fifth Avenue is about Upper East Side\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}